[Applause]
[Music]
Hello friends, the Stock Class team has
brought you a great
fundamentally strong stock that belongs to the
insurance sector. So let's
dissect it completely today.
Basically, this is a 12-month chart.
In the 12-month chart, there has been no closing below 1040
so far. If you look at the last two years, the
closing has always
been between 1200 and 1250. If you look at the candlesticks, then
if you look at the Hacken, it is
1484, which means that Hacken has become bullish right now. If you look at the six-
month candlestick, it is 1261.
And the stock has still not crossed the range of 1490 and 1500
in the last four years, as you can see, this is a range
of 1450 and 1500 for the stock and the bottom range is
1200, 1250. No doubt, the stock has gone below 1040.
But the closing has always
come above 1200 1250, so the six months low of the stock is
1314, the candlestick low is
81 and the three months low is
1381 and basically the name of this company is
Lord General Insurance Company Limited.
Some fundamentals about the company are the
market cap of the company 68000, stock price 439, book
value 230, dividend % at RO 21, RO 17.6,
face value 10 and if we look at the
share holding pattern of the company, if we look at the
promoter's share holding, it was 48.0 and now it is 48 but
this data is available here only till September,
if you see, FIIs have
sold a little, they have reached from 24 to 22,
their stake has reduced a bit
but Diya has increased the stake by the same amount, it has
gone from 16 to 18 and
if we look at the public, it is from 12 to 11  It has
landed and if we
look at who are the big sharks invested in it, then the
first name that comes up is
ICICI Group which has a
stake of 53%, SBI Group is at 4.8% and
Government Pension Fund is at 2.41%.
Basically, you know that we have been
telling you for so long that we like
channels and moving averages. This channel is
placed here which is showing a good amount of
resistance here and a good
amount of support is also showing here.
You can see these are the supports of the charts and this is the resistance. The
next support of the stock is the middle
line which is going to come at 1340. If it is
breached, the stock will come down to 1200.
This is the moving average which the stock class has
specially placed. There is only one reason behind placing 87 high of 887 high
because whenever the stock
came here, it has bounced a good amount
but as soon as it
bridged the support, it
converted into resistance.  So whenever the stock
touched here, it fell down
but again we have seen a reversal sign from here
that the stock is currently
moving above 87 high. This is AV WAP.
Basically, if you look in the app, there is a good amount of
support and resistance shown here
and this next support is coming at
1294, which means almost our range is
between 1250 to 1350. This entire
stock is still moving towards us and this is a
banding pattern.
If the stock falls below the banding pattern and comes on proper support here, then it will
come around 1250 to 1280
and if you
look at the resistance, then it will come around 20200, which
means almost if the stock comes down
to 1200, then it can almost happen. The conclusion from here is that
from this slide, you can basically
think of addition. You
can invest at 1300 if you get close to 1100.
But still I will tell you one thing, a
study.  Purpose video is not by say thank you
friends good night